<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Jared Hellings, PsyD]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Jared Hellings, PsyD]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/jared-hellings-psyd/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 04:13:45 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/jared-hellings-psyd/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Psychotherapy (also called therapy or counseling) is a process of mutual collaboration between therapist and client to identify the underlying causes of distress and find more adaptive and satisfying alternatives. Although there are many approaches to psychotherapy, research continues to demonstrate that the most crucial aspect is a strong professional relationship between client and therapist that is based on understanding, empathy, and openness. Therefore, I focus on creating a non-judgmental atmosphere that allows for an exploration of an individual’s thoughts, feelings, relationships, and life patterns. Above all, it is important that you feel understood. </p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/jared-hellings-psyd/therapy/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ed4fc2f9-dbb9-4e11-b36f-98a1bdbc729c</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 04:13:44 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Individuals seek a psychological evaluation for a variety of reasons. For example, many primary care physicians, psychiatrists, psychiatric nurse practitioners, and therapists refer their patients for evaluations in order to inform their treatment plans. In addition, individuals or parents of adolescents seek evaluations to determine the presence of learning disabilities, ADHD, or other mental health disorders that are impacting their functioning in school, work, or their social lives. </p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/jared-hellings-psyd/individuals-seek-a-psychological-evaluation-for-a-variety-of/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6045c98e-3242-4a43-bae7-4d695d511be0</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 04:13:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to my website. I am a clinical psychologist working in beautiful downtown Edmonds, WA, where I work with people of all ages to help address a range of problems. Seeking help can be a humbling and anxiety-filled experience. I encourage you to look around my website to get some answers to a few basic questions. Please contact me for additional information. </p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/jared-hellings-psyd/welcome-to-my-website-i-am-a-clinical-psychologist-working/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ca91f20a-1d25-4622-a5d7-f2aecc45cbcd</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 03:28:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>